pqrnews.com 2014-05-25

# Privacy Policy | PQR News

  * [Home](http://pqrnews.com/) /
  * Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy PQR NEWS

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [admin@pqrnews.com](mailto:admin@pqrnews.com). At pqrnews.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by pqrnews.com and how it is used. 

**_Log Files_**

Like many other Web sites, pqrnews.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. pqrnews.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
